I know you've been waiting to hear me talk about Fonny.
Fonny, what you talking about, Willis?
Fonny, I'm not the one on trial, Willis.
Fonny, nah, hold up, because you lie.
You lie.
Your Honor, can I go to the restroom?
Willis.
For those who don't have internet, TV, or Wi-Fi,
she is the district attorney who is at trial
prosecuting Trump for election interference in Georgia.
Now, she is on trial and at risk of being disqualified
from the case over misconduct allegations
because it came out that she and her fellow prosecutor
were digging into a lot more than files.
That was some of the most fascinating testimonies
I've ever watched in real time.
Now, listen, grown people be in court
and have been in court long before Fonny Willis,
and so we have had so many just examples
of interesting testimony.
Let's play some of the hits.
O.J. Simpson in a knit cap from two blocks away
is still O.J. Simpson.
It's no disguise, it makes no sense, it doesn't fit.
If it doesn't fit, you must acquit.
R.I.P. to Johnny Cochran.
All right, hit me with another one.
I did not have sexual relations with that woman,
Ms. Lewinsky.
I never told anybody to lie.
This is similar to how Fonny was like,
you said that we had a romantic relationship.
Smashing ain't romantic.
You be specific.
We up, we up, we up.